Guide to the Robert L. Bracklow Photograph Collection 1882-1918 (bulk, 1896-1905) PR 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Trappan Gift: Photograph Albums, 2
  - Subseries II.6: "Dewey Days" [Album 5], 6
    - The amateur photographer at large [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - U.S.S. Olympia [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - U.S.S. Texas [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - U.S.S. Brooklyn [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - U.S. Transport [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch from 25th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: The Call to Arms [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - Dewey Arch Group: The Army [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
    - West side of Dewey Arch [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 22, Box 22, Album 5)
  - Subseries II.7: "Dewey Arch" [Album 6], 7
    - Dewey Arch west side [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 6)
      Same image as Alland # 2049
    - Dewey Arch top from north [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 6)
      Same image as Alland # 2037
    - Dewey Arch from 5th Ave. Hotel [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 6)
      Same image as Alland # 2020
    - Madison Square Garden [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 6)
      Same image as Alland # 2083
    - Dewey Arch from South [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 6)
  - Subseries II.8: "Manhattan from within and without" [Album 7], 8
    - Site of Flatiron - 5th Ave. & 23 St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 467
    - The Fuller Building on the "Flat Iron" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 468
    - Fuller Building on the Flat Iron from Bancroft Building [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 1258
    - Seeing New York coach, 27th St. & Fifth Avenue [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 4
    - Grand Central Station [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 472
    - Croton Reservoir 5th & 42nd [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 321
    - Croton Reservoir 5th & 42nd [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 1677A
    - Croton Reservoir 5th & 42nd [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 1677
    - Croton Reservoir 5th & 42nd - three cars [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 321A
    - Site of Public Library - 5th Ave [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 1248
    - Site of Public Library - 5th Ave [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 1477
    - Washington Statue [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 1757
    - Starin Line Pier 13 N.R. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 1244
    - Boats on North River [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
      Same image as Alland # 918
    - Church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Croton Reservoir 5th & 42nd [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Unloading ice from the barge J.C. Hutchinson, near West 10th St., Hudson R. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Unloading ice barge, foot of West 10th Street, N.R. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - White Star Line Steamer "Majestic" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Starin Line Pier 13 N.R. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Boats on North River [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Boats on North River [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Boats on North River [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Brooklyn Bridge [Brooklyn Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Brooklyn Bridge [Brooklyn Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Brooklyn Bridge [Brooklyn Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
    - Boats on North River [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 7)
  - Subseries II.9: "Manhattan Old and New" [Album 8], 9
    - Spingler -Van Buren estate - large tree in West 14th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1309
    - Spingler -Van Buren estate - large tree in West 14th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 471B
    - Clinton Market from West Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1407
    - Old style doorway in Hudson Street, opposite St. John's Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 16
    - Washington Arch and Fountain, from south of 4th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1607
    - Van Buren House and old Poplar Tree - West 14th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 471A
    - Van Buren House and old Poplar Tree - West 14th Street looking west [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 471
    - Broadway looking north from 20th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1316
    - Madison Square from 5th Avenue, below 23rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 31A
    - Fuller Building, Broadway, Fifth Avenue, 22nd to 23rd Streets [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 468A
    - Supreme Court-State of New York-Appelate Division. Madison Square and 25th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1088
    - Seeing New York Coach West 27th Street and Fifh Avenue [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Broadway, looking south from 30th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1254
    - Saks & Co. and R.H.Macy & Co.'s Buildings from Broadway, near 30th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1321
    - Mansion 19 West 34 St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1234
    - Fifth Avenue, north from 28th Street - Collegiate Reformed (Marble) Church, at 29th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 935
    - Pabst Hotel in course of erection, from Seventh Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1001A
    - Fifth Avenue, south from 35 Street - Manhattan Club, and Waldorf-Astoria Hotel [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
      Same image as Alland # 1110
    - Clinton Market; Spring, Washington, Canal and West Streets [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Fountain and Washington Arch [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Fifth Avenue, north from 10th Street, "Old First Presbyterian Church" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - East side of Fifth Avenue, from 12 to 13th Streets [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Church of the Transfiguration, "the little church around the corner" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - 29th Street, west from 5th Avenue [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Pabst Hotel, from Seventh Avenue, near 41st Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Pabst Hotel, from Broadway, near 41st Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Pabst Hotel from Broadway, south of 42nd Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Pabst Hotel from 42nd Street, east of Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Broadway and 42nd Street before Pabst Hotel was thought of [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Houses in 40th Street, east of Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Broadway Theater [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Exit Hotel Pabst, from Broadway to 42nd Street, in course of demolition [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Hotel Marlborough, from 38th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Metropolitan Opera House, from 38th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
    - Pabst Hotel in course of demolition [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 23, Album 8)
  - Subseries II.10: "Riverside Drive, Madison Square" [Album 9], 10
    - Old Station for passengers and freight of the Hudson River and New York Central Railroad [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1239
    - Setting up the frame for Flatiron Building [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1433
    - Wm. N. Seward Statue, Madison Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1119
    - Roscoe Conkling Statue, Madison Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1769
    - Young Men's Christian Association Building 4th Avenue & 23rd Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1055
    - Lyceum Theater - Madison Sq. Tower [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1389
    - Claremont Hotel, Riverside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1422
    - Grant's Tomb and the Claremont [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1127
    - Viaduct Riverside Drive over 125th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1388
    - Shanty photo studio Riverside Drive near 122nd Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 564
    - W. J. Hancock bust [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1332
    - German Yacht "Hohenzollern" at foot of 34th Street, North River [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 308
    - Yacht "Hohenzollern" and steamer "Krouprinz Wilhelm," at foot of 34th Street, North River [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1513
    - Yacht "Hohenzollern" and steamer "Krouprinz Wilhelm," with military escort for Prince Henry of Prussia [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1513A
    - Yacht "Hohenzollern" & steamer "Krouprinz Wilhelm" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
      Same image as Alland # 1101
    - Soldiers & Sailors Monument, Riverside Drive & 89th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - Old house - 111 Street near Amsterdam Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - D. F. Tiemann houses, Claremont Ave. near 127th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - Statue [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - German Yacht "Hohenzollern" at foot of 34th Street, North River [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - Yacht "Hohenzollern" & steamer "Krouprinz Wilhelm" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - Looking west through East 25th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - Statue "Force" - Appellate Court [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - Looking eastward from Madison Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - Statue "Wisdom" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
    - [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 9)
  - Subseries II.11: "Gotham" [Album 10], 11
    - Statue of John Ericson [Ericsson] designer of the "Monitor" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 122
    - Barge Office, Battery Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 112
    - Edifice of the Evangelist Lutheran Church of the Holy Trinity 43-47 West 21 Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1751
    - Reformed Presbyterian Church, West 12th Street, between 6th and 7th Aves. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1748A
    - 13th Street Presbyterian Church, between 6th and 7th Avenues [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1748
    - Cloud studies 1, Tug St. Patrick [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 326
    - Cloud studies 2, off Turtle Bay [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1764
    - Cloud studies 4, Williamsburgh shore [Williamsburg Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1525
    - Cloud studies 6, Brooklyn Navy Yard [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1526
    - Cloud studies 7 [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1525A
    - Cloud studies 8, from ferryboat [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 326A
    - U.S. Army Building - main entrance, Whitehall St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1676
    - Bowling Green contrasts. Stevens House - Columbia building [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 215
    - New Street - canyon - from Beaver Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1470
    - Broad Street - canyon - from Beaver Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 228
    - United States Sub Treasury - Broad & Wall Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 1592
    - Wall Street, from Broad Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 210
    - One of the last vegetable "truck" gardens, West End Avenue & 89th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
      Same image as Alland # 552
    - Two houses 25 & 27 West 21st Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
    - Cloud studies 3, new East River Bridge [Williamsburg Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
    - Cloud studies 5, "It blew half a gale" - and the bridge moved [Williamsburg Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
    - Cloud studies 9, from ferryboat [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
    - Cloud studies 10, East River [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
    - Old fashioned residence, Riverside Drive & 100th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 10)
  - Subseries II.12: "New Rochelle, Hunt's Point, New York, Ravenswood" [Album 11], 12
    - Thomas Paine monument [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
      Same image as Alland # 1488
    - Woman's Hospital, Park Avenue, 49-50 Streets [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
      Same image as Alland # 1800
    - Spire of the Reformed Church, Fifth Avenue, corner of 48th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
      Same image as Alland # 1243
    - Railroad Branch, Y.M.C.A., Madison Ave and 45th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
      Same image as Alland # 1294
    - Old houses, 122 and 124 William Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
      Same image as Alland # 1073
    - Blackwell's Island, looking southwest from a point a little farther north [Roosevelt Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
      Same image as Alland # 964
    - Thomas Paine monument [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - The lane and the Thomas Paine monument [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Old stone house [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Cemetary at Hunt's Point [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Grave of Joseph Rodman Drake, M.D. [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - The road from the point [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Farm house [West Farms (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Thomas Paine monument [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Thomas Paine monument and lane [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Rose Hill, North St. [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Residence on Rose Hill [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Blackwell's Island, looking south from the foot of Webster Avenue [Roosevelt Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Blackwell House, built about 1664 [Ravenswood (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Blackwell House - from the southwest [Ravenswood (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
    - Cottage, Broadway and Boulevard [Astoria (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 24, Album 11)
  - Subseries II.13: "Lorelei Fountain - Heine Monument" [Album 12], 13
    - Lorelei Fountain, side view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
      Same image as Alland # 728A
    - Lorelei Fountain, side view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
      Same image as Alland # 728 G
    - Lorelei Fountain, showing damage done by some vandal [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
      Same image as Alland # 728B
    - Lorelei Fountain, damaged [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
      Same image as Alland # 728F
    - Lorelei Fountain, close up view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
      Same image as Alland # 728E
    - Lorelei Fountain, enclosed by fence [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
      Same image as Alland # 7228D
    - Lorelei Fountain, enclosed by fence [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
      Same image as Alland # 728C
    - Lorelei Fountain, showing Lyrical Poetry offering rose [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain, side view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain, day after the unveiling [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain, day after the unveiling [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain, day after the unveiling [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain, damaged [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain, rear view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
    - Lorelei Fountain [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 12)
  - Subseries II.14: "Fort Washington, N.Y. and a bit of Fort Lee, N.J." [Album 13], 14
    - 9 miles from New York 1764 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1908 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
      Same image as Alland # 1279
    - Fort Washington Monument [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
      Same image as Alland # 1813
    - Country house of James Gordon Bennett, Fort Washington [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
      Same image as Alland # 975
    - Quartz snake in rock, in Cooper Street, near Emerson St. [], 1908 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
      Same image as Alland # 1487
    - Audubon Monument, Trinity Cemetery [], 1908 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
    - Audubon Monument, Trinity Cemetery [], 1908 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
    - Presbyterian Church - 155th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1908 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
    - Battle Lane, Fort Washington [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
    - Battle Lane, Fort Washington through gate [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1908 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)
    - Battle Lane, Fort Washington [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Offsite-box 23-30, Box 25, Album 13)